

+1 707 321 3334
sanjwich@gmail.com
Kochstraße 117
04277 Leipzig Germany
Finland/USA dual citizen

SKILLS

Ruby
Ruby on Rails
Javascript
HTML5/CSS3/SASS
PostgreSQL/SQLite
Git/Github
Heroku
RESTful API's
Test Driven Development

LANGUAGES

English - **Native/Fluent**German - **B1**Finnish - **B1**

VOLUNTEER POSITIONS

@NorthBrooklynAngels, volunteer

@FormulaFemme, former team member

MEDIA

Portfolio

<u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

SANJA WETZEL

Full Stack Web Developer

I am a junior full stack web developer with experience designing, building and maintaining production applications who can handle **difficult technical challenges** and solve interesting real-world problems. My 17 years of experience in the service industry in a variety of management and **customer-focused positions** has finely tuned my **interpersonal communication**, creative problem solving, and **anticipating client needs**. I am transitioning out of the industry to pursue my interest in web development with the associated **technical skills necessary to thrive** in this rapidly changing field.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon Berlin Batch 398, Web Development - April-June 2020 San Francisco State University, Bachelor of Music, cum laude - Class of '09

EXPERIENCE

Founder, NightCAP Brooklyn; Brooklyn, NY - 2014-Present

I founded this social cycling organization for riders who aren't traditionally represented in bicycle culture.

NightCAP (which stands for Cycling Against the Patriarchy) exists for the trans and non-binary community, and allied cis women who agree that life is better on two wheels.

Bartender, Bar Great Harry; Brooklyn, NY - 2014-2020

Expert knowledge of craft beer offerings, local breweries, and neighborhood happenings.

Cultivated lasting relationships with regulars, fellow industry folks, and representatives from the region.

Applied excellent organizational and multitasking abilities to handle simultaneous customer, team and business needs while avoiding unnecessary delays or errors.

Retail Manager, Blue Bottle Coffee; San Francisco, CA & New York, NY – 2009-2014

I initially worked as a barista at the SFMOMA café, then moved up quickly and became Retail Manager of the SFMOMA location in less than a year.

Blue Bottle selected me to open and manage a brand new café in Tribeca, NY. I managed the Tribeca café, my tasks included staffing, inventory management, quality control, as well as professional networking with everyone from roasters and baristas to CEOs.

PROJECTS

www.welcome-mentors.com

A web application designed to help working professionals relocating to Berlin by providing useful articles, resources, and connections with mentors that have already made the move.

www.bike-match-sweetening.herokuapp.com

An AirBnB clone to pair cyclists with bikes for rent in their preferred size and style.